Rajat Saini



+91-8130813864



rajatuxd@gmail.com



M <u>medium.com/@r</u>ajatuxd

Lead UX Designer

dribbble.com/rajatuxd, behance.net/rajatuxd



About Me

I would describe myself as someone who is passionate to provide my users visually pleasing, easy to use interfaces. From the past 8+ years, I have been designing mobile and web products. I have been always appreciated a user's advocacy in my work experiences. With all this experience, I'm still keen to learn more about UX/UI and hence provide my best to the organization.



Tools

Photoshop			\circ
Adobe XD			\circ
Illustrator		0	\bigcirc
Sketch		0	0
After Effect		0	0
Google Analytics		0	\bigcirc
Figma			



Experience

Lead UX Designer

2020 - Present

Mckinley Rice

Lead teams of 8+ development, engineering, product, design and marketing professionals in all phases of custom product solutions

UX Designer

2020 - 2020

Coalshastra (B2B)

Created MVP in 6 months in the SaaS, Lead a team of 4 people.

UX/UI Designer

2018 - 2020

Ferns N Petals PVT LTD (B2C)

Successfully delivered 20+ projects, Handled the entire project of FNP (Dubai & Singapore)

UX/UI Designer

2016 - 2018

Navyug Infosolutions PVT LTD

Delivered 30+ Projects, Handled 20+ Clients in 2.5 years, Time Management

UI Designer

2015 - 2016

Freelancing

Designed visual mockup for mobile application (los & Android), Website and responsive design.

UI Designer

2014 - 2015

Iyogi Technical Servcies

Created User Interface softwares



Skills

Jira & Agile Soft.			
SWOT Analysis			0
Quality Assurance			\bigcirc
Interpersonal Skills		\bigcirc	0
Risk Management		\bigcirc	\circ
SEO		\circ	0
Digital Marketing		0	0



Education

Btech 2009-2013

Kurukshetra University

(ECE-61%)

Senior Secondary (12th Class)

2008 - 2009

Kendriya Vidyalaya Sangathan

(CBSE - 61%)

Secondary (10th Class)

2006 - 2007

Kendriya Vidyalaya Sangathan

(CBSE - 63%)



Languages

English

Hindi